Sigma Pi Phi, Beta Psi Boulé; Records apap333
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Sigma Pi Phi, Beta Psi Boulé Records
1983-2021
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap333
10.76 cubic ft. plus digital contents of CDs and floppy disk
The Sigma Pi Phi, Beta Psi Boulé Records document the history and day-to-day operations of the Beta Psi Boulé. A professional fraternity, Sigma Pi Phi was founded on May 15, 1904 in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania and its members are distinguished African American men with college and graduate degrees. Beta Psi is the fraternity's 69th Boulé founded on May 5, 1984 in the Capital District of New York.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted with the exception of select files located in Series 1, including the official meeting minutes of the organization.
Acquisition Information
Sigma Pi Phi, Beta Psi Boulé donated all of the materials in this collection to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives beginning in November 2012. The organization donated additional records annually between 2013-2021.
Administrative History
Sigma Pi Phi, Beta Psi Boulé is the Capital District's chapter of the nation's oldest Greek-letter organization comprised of college-educated and professional African American men. Founded in Philadelphia on May 15, 1904, the Sigma Pi Phi fraternity is referred to as the Boulé which is Greek for a council of noblemen. Its members are called Archons and their wives are Archousia. As of 2012, Sigma Pi Phi had over 5,000 members in 129 "chapters", known as member Boulés, throughout the United States, the United Kingdom and the Bahamas. A secret society, Sigma Pi Phi has begun to release information about itself to the public, however, it still holds to confidentiality within the organization.
The national office is the Grand Boulé with five regional Boulés to represent the Northeast, Southeast, Central, Western, and Pacific regions with individual Boulés within each. Sigma Pi Phi's elected executive officers are referred to by Greek titles. The local Boulé head is the Sire Archon, and there is a Sire Archon-Elect, and an Immediate Past Sire Archon. The Grammateus is the executive secretary, the Thesauristes is the treasurer, the Rhetoricus arranges meetings and programs, the Agogos heads the constitution and by-laws committee and the Grapter is the official news reporter of the Boulé in charge of news and editorial duties. The Grand Boulé's elected executive officers are Grand Officers with the title Grand before their post and the regional Boulés' elected executive officers have the respective Region added before the position title. For example, Northeast Region Sire Archon would be the head of the Northeast Region.
The Beta Psi Boulé of the Capital Region was established on May 5, 1984. It has been active in and supportive of the Capital District community for more than a quarter century hosting annual community events, supporting charitable initiatives for various causes and sponsoring endowments directly from Beta Psi or from the Sigma Pi Phi Foundation. The University at Albany Spellman Achievement Award is a Beta Psi scholarship endowment created in honor of the late Seth Spellman Jr., one of the founders of the Beta Psi Boulé. The members of Beta Psi are high ranking officials in the Capital District community, including faculty and administrators in area Universities, business owners and other professionals with postgraduate educations and titles.
Scope and Contents
The Sigma Pi Phi, Beta Psi Boulé Records document the history of the Capital District's chapter of the nation's oldest Greek-letter organization comprised of college-educated and professional African American men. The collection contains Sigma Pi Phi, Beta Psi charter certificates, administrative records including meeting agendas and minutes, notices, correspondences and financial reports, the Northeast Regional and Grand Boulé conference materials, photographs, subject files, executive committee records, and Sigma Pi Phi's official publication The Boulé Journal.
The collection also includes records of Beta Psi community involvement and contributions to the Capital Region, member achievements and recognition, annual events, and articles of memorabilia. The collection covers the years of existence of the Beta Psi Boulé, from 1984 onward. There is a nearly complete run of the publication The Boulé Journal.
Separated Materials
Archivists transferred the following titles: the two volume monograph The History of Sigma Pi Phi: First of the African-American Greek-Letter Fraternities by Charles Wesley and Hobart Sidney Jarrett; Son of Prince Edward County by Twitty J. Styles; and The Thornton Family by Maurice Thornton to the book division of Special Collections. The catalog records for these monographs already were or will be included in the University Library Catalog.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1 - Administration, 1984-2020
Series 2 - Subject Files, 1984-2019, Undated
Series 3 - Special Events, 1985-2018
Series 4 - Publications, 1983-2019
Series 1 and 4 are arranged chronologically. Series 2 and Series 3 are arranged alphabetically.
Related Materials
Additional materials about the Sigma Pi Phi, Beta Psi Boulé Records may be found in the papers of Bernard Ashe at the the Schomburg Center for Research in Black Culture.
African Americans and Civil Rights Organizations; Albany, New York; African Americans--Education (Higher); African American Greek letter societies; African American fraternal organizations; African American college graduates--New York (State)--Albany (N.Y.); Albany (N.Y.); By-laws (administrative records); Constitutions; Ritual Objects; Charters; Administrative records; Minutes (administrative records); Agendas (administrative records); Newsletters; Financial Records; Membership lists; Press Releases; Correspondence; Programs (documents); Photographs; Sigma Pi Phi, Beta Psi Boulé; Sigma Pi Phi
- Administration, 1984-2020; 1; 2.0 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the Beta Psi Boulé's administrative records. The materials cover the beginning of the charter process for the Beta Psi Boulé to present day. The files consist of the Boulé's day-to-day administrative records for 1984-2017 with the exception of the year 2010. The series consists of charter plans, certificates and reports, administrative records, Beta Psi Executive Committee documents, financial reports, general meeting minutes, correspondences, memorandums, notices and agendas as well as documents from some of the Boulé's committees. The bulk of the documents were created by the officers and members of Beta Psi Boulé and the officers of the Grand Boulé with the exception of some correspondence and event brochures of other Greek letter fraternities and sororities, Capital District businesses and charitable organizations.
  As the majority of administrative records were created by the executive committee of the fraternity, please note that these officers are elected by the members of the Boulé every two years. This change in record creators and keepers is reflected in the way meeting packets are arranged year by year. Beta Psi had its fewest members immediately after it received its charter. Therefore the first few years of administrative records are filed into single folders by the creator. As the Boulé grew and officers changed, record keeping changed in the way the materials were created, distributed and retained. Some years' agendas were sent out with notices, financial reports were stored with meeting minutes, and executive and general meetings were kept together. In other years, the agendas and meeting minutes are together. Sometimes minutes, agendas, and financial reports all have their own folders. The archivists retained all these variations of original order record keeping for all years.
  The transformation of the official Beta Psi header and the Sigma Pi Phi insignia can be mapped over the years by the documents in this series.
  - Charter, 1984 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 1)
  - Administrative Records - [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 2)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - Administrative Records - [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 3)
  - Administrative Records - [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 4)
  - Administrative Records - [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 5)
  - Administrative Records - [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 7)
  - Financial Reports, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 8)
  - Meeting Minutes and Notices - [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 10)
  - Meeting Minutes and Notices - [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 11)
  - Administrative Records - [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 12)
  - Administrative Records - [RESTRICTED], 1992 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 13)
  - Administrative Records - [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 14)
  - Membership Directory - [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 16)
  - Financial Reports, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 17)
  - Meeting Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 18)
  - Meeting Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 19)
  - Membership Directory - [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 21)
  - Meeting Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 23)
  - Meeting Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 1997 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 25)
  - Financial Reports, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 26)
  - Meeting Minutes and Agendas - [RESTRICTED], 1998 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 28)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1999 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 29)
  - Meeting Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 1999 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 30)
  - Meeting Notices and Agendas, 1999 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 31)
  - Correspondence and Memos, 2000 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 32)
  - Financial Reports, 2000 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 33)
  - Meeting Minutes and Agendas - [RESTRICTED], 2000 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 35)
  - Executive Committee Minutes and Agendas - [RESTRICTED], 2001 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 36)
  - Financial Reports, 2001 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 37)
  - Meeting Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 2001 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 38)
  - Meeting Notices and Agendas, 2001 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 39)
  - Memos, 2001 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 40)
  - Social Action Committee, 2001 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 42)
  - Executive Committee Minutes and Agendas - [RESTRICTED], 2002 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 43)
  - Financial Reports, 2002 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 44)
  - Forms, 2002 (Box 1 (1-Administration), Folder 45)
  - Meeting Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 2002 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 1)
  - Meeting Notices and Agendas, 2002 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 2003 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Notices and Agendas - [RESTRICTED], 2003 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 5)
  - Financial Reports, 2003 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 6)
  - Meeting Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 2003 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 7)
  - Meeting Notices and Agendas - [RESTRICTED], 2003 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Documents, 2003 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 9)
  - 20th Anniversary, 2004 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee Minutes and Agendas - [RESTRICTED], 2004 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 12)
  - Financial Reports, 2004 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 13)
  - Meeting Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 2004 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 14)
  - Meeting Notices and Agendas - [RESTRICTED], 2004 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 15)
  - Meeting Planning CD Project, 2004 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 16)
  - Memos, 2004 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 17)
  - Boulé Golf Committee, 2005 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence and Memos, 2005 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 19)
  - Executive Committee Minutes and Agendas - [RESTRICTED], 2005 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 20)
  - Financial Reports, 2005 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 21)
  - Meeting Agendas, 2005 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 22)
  - Meeting Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 2005 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 23)
  - Meeting Notices, 2005 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 25)
  - Executive Committee Agendas, 2006 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 26)
  - Executive Committee Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 2006 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 27)
  - Financial Reports, 2006 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 28)
  - Meeting Agendas, 2006 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 29)
  - Meeting Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 2006 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 30)
  - Memos, 2006 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 31)
  - Strategic Plan, 2006 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 32)
  - Committee Reports, 2007 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 34)
  - Executive Committee - [RESTRICTED], 2007 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 35)
  - Financial Reports, 2007 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 36)
  - Boulé Foundation Receipts, 2008 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 2008 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 38)
  - Executive Committee - [RESTRICTED], 2008 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 39)
  - Financial Reports, 2008 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 40)
  - Meeting Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 2008 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 41)
  - Social Action Committee, 2008 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 42)
  - Bank Account Transfer - [RESTRICTED], 2009 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, 2009 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 44)
  - Executive Committee, 2009 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 45)
  - Meeting Minutes and Agendas - [RESTRICTED], 2009 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, 2011 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 47)
  - Financial Reports, 2011 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 48)
  - Meeting Agenda, 2011 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 49)
  - Financial Reports, 2012 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 50)
  - Report on Archives at SUNY Albany, 2012 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 51)
  - Ad Hoc Committee, 2013 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 52)
  - Business Meeting Agenda, 2013 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 53)
  - Executive Committee Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 2013 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 54)
  - Financial Reports, 2013 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 55)
  - Meeting Packets - [RESTRICTED], 2013 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 56)
  - Financial Reports, 2014 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 57)
  - Meeting Packets - [RESTRICTED], 2014 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 58)
  - Financial Reports, 2015 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 59)
  - Meeting Packets - [RESTRICTED], 2015 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 60)
  - Meeting Packets and Financial Reports - [RESTRICTED], 2016 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 61)
  - Correspondence, 2017 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 62)
  - Meeting Packets and Financial Reports - [RESTRICTED], 2017 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 63)
  - Policies, 2017 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 64)
  - Meeting Packets - [RESTRICTED], 2018 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 65)
  - Meeting Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 2019 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 66)
  - Meeting Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 2020 (Box 2 (1-Administration), Folder 67)
- Subject Files, 1984-2021; 2; 3.22 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains records of Beta Psi Annual Membership reports to the Grand Boulé, Christmas is for the Archousai and other annual events, some social action committee documents for specific community initiatives and interests (minutes and agendas for the committee can be found in Series 1 - Administration), Boulé Foundation and Beta Psi charitable initiative documents, and the creation and arrangement of the University at Albany Spellman Achievement Award, a scholarship program endowed by Beta Psi in honor of the late Seth Spellman Jr., a founders of the Beta Psi Boulé. The series also includes records of events sponsored or supported by the Beta Psi Boulé, documents from the nominating committee later renamed the Membership Council, revised constitutions, by-laws, and rituals of the fraternity and a Sigma Pi Phi protocol manual.
  - American Association For Affirmative Action, Regional Director Gavel, Undated (Artifact-box 1)
  - Annual Events, 1996; 1998-2002; 2005-2006; 2013-2015 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Annual Events: Christmas, 1990; 1992-1993; 1997-1998 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Annual Events: Christmas, 1999-2006; 2011-2013 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Annual Events: Christmas, 2014-2019 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 4-5)
  - Annual Events: Christmas Party Photographs, 2004 (Cd 1)
  - Annual Events: Christmas Party Photographs, 2014 (Cd 4)
  - Annual Events: Photograph Albums, Undated (Oversized 1)
  - Annual Events: Negative Film Strips, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Annual Events: Photos, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Annual Membership Reports, 1985-2007 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 8-9)
  - Ashe, Bernard, 2017; 2020 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Beta Psi Active Roster, 1992-2000; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Beta Psi Banner, Undated (Oversized 2)
  - Beta Psi Delegates to the Grand Boulé, 1986; 1988; 2002 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Beta Psi Endowments and the Boulé Foundation, 1988-2011 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Beta Psi Foundation Scholarship Award, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Beta Psi Member Name Stickers, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Beta Psi Member Recognition, the University at Albany, 2007; 2012 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Beta Psi Membership Directory, 2001-2002; 2005-2006 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Boule Foundation, 2016; 2018-2019 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Boulé News, 1990; 1993; 2000-2003; 2006; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 19-20)
  - Candidates for the Northeastern Boulé, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - A Celebration of Life for Lawrence Cornelius Burwell, Jr., 2001 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Conference Planning Guidelines, 2004 (Floppy-disk 1)
  - Establishment of New Subordinate Boulés, 1984-2005 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Grammateus Guides, 1998-2000 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Grand Sire Archon Nominees, 1990-2005; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Habitat for Humanity Recognition, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Heritage, John, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Homecoming Fellowship and Thanksgiving Service for Reverend James E.F. Lawrence, 2016 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Inaugural Scholarship Gala, 2016 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - March on Washington, Maurice Thornton, 2013 (Dvd 1)
  - "Maryland, My Maryland" or "O Tannenbaum, O Tannenbaum": Thoughts on the Boulé Song and Parting Hymn, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Membership Directory and By-Laws, 2013 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Membership Directory and Lists, 2009-2011 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Membership Council/Nominating Committee, 1984-1988; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Membership Council/Nominating Committee, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Membership Council/Nominating Committee, 1991-1993; 2000-2002; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Membership Council/Nominating Committee, 2004-2005; 2008-2009; 2011; 2017; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Memorial Service, 2016 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - New York State Martin Luther King, Jr. Commission and Institute for Nonviolence: Certificate of Appreciation, 1993-1994 (Oversized 3)
  - Northeast Region Best Practices Guide (folders 1-2 of 3), 2008 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 38-39)
  - Northeast Region Best Practices Guide (folder 3 of 3), 2008 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Revised Rituals Manual, 1997 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Rituals, 1984; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Sigma Pi Phi Beta Psi Boulé Files, 1997; 1999-2004 (Cd 2)
    The files were compiled by the Beta Psi Boulé for archival use and contain records created from 1997 to 2004. The original order of the files was kept since the creator grouped many related files into folders. The files include records of the 15th Regional Conference, the Beta Nu Conference web materials, Beta Psi administrative records, documents from the Seth Spellman Fund, Boulé graphics, photographs, programs and lists from annual events, rituals, and constitutions and by-laws.
  - Sigma Pi Phi Beta Psi Boulé Constitution and By-Laws, 1999; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Sigma Pi Phi Beta Psi Boulé Stationaries, Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Sigma Pi Phi Constitution and By-Laws, 1985; 1990; 1992; 1996 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Sigma Pi Phi Constitution and By-Laws Member Binders, 1985; 1992 (Artifact-box 2)
  - Sigma Pi Phi Fraternity, A Guide for Implementing the Fraternity's Strategic Plan, 2010 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Sigma Pi Phi Protocol Manual, 2010 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Dr. Leonard A. Slade, Jr., 1993-2014 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Dr. Leonard A. Slade, Jr., 2013; 2015; 2018 (Flat-file 1)
  - Dr. Leonard A. Slade, Jr., 2015-2019 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Dr. Leonard A. Slade, Jr., 2020-2021; Undated (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Dr. Leonard A. Slade, Jr., Albany Public Library Literary Legends, 2016 (Video-tape 2)
  - Dr. Leonard Slade, Jr., Poems from God put a Rainbow in the Sky, University at Albany Alumni House, 2014 (Dvd 2)
  - Social Action Programs of Delta Theta Boulé, Las Vegas, Nevada, Undated (Dvd 3)
  - Soirée, 2013 (Dvd 4)
  - Soirée, including Times Union Article about Beta Psi Boulé, 2013 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Sponsored Events (1 of 2), 1993; 1998-2001; 2003-2005; 2011 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Sponsored Events (2 of 2), 1993; 1998-2001; 2003-2005; 2011 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Sponsored Events: The Jackie Wilson Story, ca. 2003 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Statement of Activities, 2004-2007 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Dr. Connie Styles - 80th, 2014 (Dvd 5)
  - Dr. Twitty Styles, 2019; 2021 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Thirtieth Anniversary Celebration, Beta Psi Boulé, 2014 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 8)